Day 35
Now when i was young boy
At the age of five.
There's 1 stop left here.
O
Marcelon.
Yeah
a child.
What's the plan?
If I'm prospecting for a customer selling High ticket this is great.
I can make money and get closer to my goal of starting a business.
Trying to prospect on the High ticket I discovered that there
is a problem pattern and it turns out to be the same.
This one is very clear positioning this one he wants to have more
clients here positioning everyone has the same positioning problem
because why do they have positioning problem because they don't
know how to tell story a way to unite everyone.
This problem is the same I create a method if the method achieves.
João Maria José Antônio everyone I climb.
That's it
Sitting on our Side.
People don't know how to tell a good story,
they don't know how to position themselves both on social networks and to be
able to talk more about the brand to be able to create ideas for
more money they have on their table.
I think I'll get sucked in.
Is it on?
I'm thinking to myself man.
So if the pattern is the same and if I have a method I can scale I need
to think of something that I can have more sales volume at a more affordable
price but at the same time optimize my time and effort.
And then yes I do the same thing as I did with truffles.
Make it passive.
Now I need to think about what.
How can I do this?
Is it on?
I think that's where the game is brother
what a doubt bro?
I think I had 1 idea.